A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, General Correspondence FA735
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1960
  - Roth, Andrew W. (Mrs.), 1960 (Reel C-1405)
  - Ruanda-Urundi, 1960 (Reel C-1405)
  - Rutgers University, 1960 (Reel C-1405)
  - Ruth, Joseph P., 1960 (Reel C-1405)
  - SA-SZ [General File]: S - Schultz, 1960 (Reel C-1405)
  - SA-SZ [General File]: Schultz - Singleton, 1960 (Reel C-1406)
  - SA-SZ [General File]: Singleton - Stercho, 1960 (Reel C-1407)
  - SA-SZ [General File]: Stercho - SZ, 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - Saint..., 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - Salem College, 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - Sales, Edouard, 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - San..., 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - San Francisco, 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - San Francisco River Basin, 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - San Francisco State College, 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - Sao Paulo, University of, 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - Save the Children Federation, 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - Schedemann, K. Fa., 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - Schmidt..., 1960 (Reel C-1408)
  - Selvin, Hanan C., 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Sementovsky, George, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Senate..., 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Senate Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Senate Foreign Relations Committee, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Senate Subcommittee on Problems of the Aging and Aged, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Sieger, Roy, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Sister..., 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Society..., 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Society for Applied Anthropology, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Society for International Development, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Somers, Herman M., 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - South..., 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - South Africa, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - South Bend Civic Planning Association, Inc., 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - South Central Independent Colleges Association of Chemists, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Southeast Asia Treaty Organizations, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Southern..., 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Southern California, University of, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Southern Illinois University, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Springfield College (Massachusetts), 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Stanford Research Institute, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - Stanford University, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - State Charities Aid Association, 1960 (Reel C-1409)
  - State Department, 1960 (Reel C-1410)
  - Stetson University (Florida), 1960 (Reel C-1410)
  - Stevens..., 1960 (Reel C-1410)
  - Stewart..., 1960 (Reel C-1410)
  - Stone..., 1960 (Reel C-1410)
  - Stone, Shepard, 1960 (Reel C-1410)
  - Supervisors Inter-County Committee, 1960 (Reel C-1410)
  - Sutton, Francis X., 1960; Sutton, Francis X. (Francis Xavier) (Reel C-1410)
    Includes papers by Francis X. Sutton: "Problems and Strategy of Research in Less Developed Countries"; "Authority and Authoritarianism in the New Africa"; and "The Ford Foundation Development Program in Arica", dated 1960.
  - Syracuse University, 1960 (Reel C-1410)
  - Syria, 1960 (Reel C-1410)
  - Szymczak, M.S., 1960 (Reel C-1410)
  - TA-TZ [General File]: T - Tool, 1960 (Reel C-1410)
  - TA-TZ [General File]: Tool - TZ, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Tanganyika, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Taylor, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Teachers College Record, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Technical..., 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Technical Assistance Information Clearing House, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Texas, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Texas, University of, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Thailand, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Theatre, Inc., 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Thomas..., 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Thopmson..., 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Thurger, Clarence E., 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Tibet, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Toledo, University of, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Toronto, University of, Press, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Trinity..., 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Tufts University, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Tulane University, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Tunisia, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Turkey, 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Turner..., 1960 (Reel C-1411)
  - Twentieth Century Fund, 1960 (Reel C-1412)
  - Twin City Area Education Television Corporation, 1960 (Reel C-1412)
  - UA-UZ [General File], 1960 (Reel C-1412)
  - UNESCO, 1960 (Reel C-1412)
  - Union..., 1960 (Reel C-1412)
  - United..., 1960 (Reel C-1412)
  - United Arab Republic, 1960 (Reel C-1412)
  - United Nations, 1960 (Reel C-1412)
  - United Parents Associations, 1960 (Reel C-1412)
  - United States, 1960 (Reel C-1412)
  - United States Information Agency, 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - United States National Committee - International Commission on Irrigation and Drainage, 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - University College..., 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - University College (Ibadan, Nigeria), 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - University College of Swansea, 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - University College of the West Indies, 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - University of the Valley, 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - Utah, University of, 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - Uyehara, Cecil H., 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - VA-VZ [General File], 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - Van..., 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - Vanderbilt University, 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - Virginia, University of, 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - Voice of America, 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - Von..., 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - WA-WZ [General File]: W - Warner, 1960 (Reel C-1413)
  - WA-WZ [General File]: Warner - Workmen, 1960 (Reel C-1414)
  - WA-WZ [General File]: Workmen - WZ, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Walker, W. Hugh, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Ward, F. Champion, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Washington..., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Washington and Lee University, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Washington, University of, (Seattle), 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Washington, University of (St. Louis), 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Watson..., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Wayne State University, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Weaver, John Henry, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Webb School of California, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Webster College, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Welfare Planning Council, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Wellesley College, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Wesleyan College, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - West..., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - West Virginia..., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - West Virginia University, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Western..., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - WGBH-TV (Boston), 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - White..., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - White, Clarence Cameron, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - White, Theodore H., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Williams..., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Williams, Roger J., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Wisconsin, State College of, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Wisconsin, University of, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Women..., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Woods..., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - World..., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Wyzanski, Charles E., 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - XA-XZ [General File], 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - YA-YZ [General File], 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Yale University, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Yarmolinsky, Adam, 1960 (Reel C-1415)
  - Young..., 1960 (Reel C-1416)
  - Young, Lloyd, 1960 (Reel C-1416)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, 1960 (Reel C-1416)
  - Yudelman, Montague, 1960 (Reel C-1416)
  - ZA-ZZ [General File], 1960 (Reel C-1416)
  - Bibliography of Related Materials, General Correspondence, 1960 (Reel C-1416)
    List of books, pamphlets, articles, reports, etc. related to the General Correspondence files for 1960.
- General Correspondence, 1961
  A bibliography of related books, pamphlets, articles, reports, etc. related to the General Correspondence files for 1961 is filed at the end of this series.
  - Correspondence filed by Program/Division (A-H)
    Arrangement
    All correspondence filed under A-H was arranged under an appropriate program or division, then filed alphabetically. The remaining correspondence, filed under I-Z was filed in a single alphabetical range regardless of program or division.
    - Non-Program Related Correspondence
      - A – HEN, 1961 (Page C-1417)
    - Overseas Development / South & Southeast Asia (OD/SSEA)
      - A- H, 1961 (Reel C-1418)
    - Overseas Development / Latin American and Caribbean (OD/LAC)
      - A- H, 1961 (Reel C-1418)
    - Overseas Division / Near East & Africa (OD/NEA)
      - A – B, 1961 (Reel C-1418)
      - C – H, 1961 (Reel C-1419)
    - Overseas Development (OD)
      - A - E, 1961 (Reel C-1419)
      - F - H, 1961 (Reel C-1420)
    - International Training and Research (ITR)
      - A - H, 1961 (Reel C-1420)
    - Public Affairs (PA)
      - A – B, 1961 (Reel C-1420)
      - C – H, 1961 (Reel C-1421)
    - Science and Engineering (SE)
      - A - H, 1961 (Reel C-1421)
    - Economic Development and Administration Program (EDA)
      - A – B, 1961 (Reel C-1421)
      - C - H, 1961 (Reel C-1422)
    - Humanities and Arts (HA)
      - A – H, 1961 (Reel C-1422)
    - Office of Reports
      - A – H, 1961 (Reel C-1423)
    - International Affairs (IA)
      - A - H, 1961 (Reel C-1423)
    - Education Program
      - A – B, 1961 (Reel C-1423)
      - C – H, 1961 (Reel C-1424)
  - Correspondence not filed by Program/Division (H-Z)
    - Hill..., 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - Hill, F. F., 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - Hogg Foundation for Mental Health, 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - Howard..., 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - Hudson, Bradford B., 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - IA-IZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - Illinois Committee for Cooperation in Higher Education, 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - Illinois, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - India, 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - Indiana University, 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - Indonesia, 1961 (Reel C-1425)
    - Institute..., 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Institute for Group and Society Development, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Institute for International Education, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Institute for Religions and Social Studies, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Inter-American Development Bank, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences (Costa Rica), 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - International..., 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - International Affairs Program, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - International Business Machines (IBM), 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - International Cooperation Administration, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - International Training and Research (ITR), 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - International Training and Research (ITR) Fellowships, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - International Committee of Scientific Management, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Iowa, State University of, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Iran, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Iraq, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Israel, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - JA-JZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Jackson State College, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Japan, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Johnson..., 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Jones..., 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Jordan, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Jordan, Zbigniew, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Journal of Engineering Education, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - Justice Department, 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - KA-KN [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1426)
    - KO-KZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Kampmeier, Roland, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Kansas Board of Regents, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Kansas, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Kazamias, Andreas M., 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Kenya, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - King..., 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Kruglak, Theodore E., 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - LA-LZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Latin America, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Latin American Faculty of Social Sciences, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Lebanon, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Lee…, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Leeds, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Lehigh University, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Lewis…, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Library of Congress, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Loyola University, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - Luther College, 1961 (Reel C-1427)
    - MA-MZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1428)
    - Malaya, 1961 (Reel C-1428)
    - Malaya, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1428)
    - Martin…, 1961 (Reel C-1428)
    - Mason…, 1961 (Reel C-1428)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1961 (Reel C-1428)
    - Mayor's Conference on Youth and Work, 1961 (Reel C-1428)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Co. Inc., 1961 (Reel C-1428)
    - Mendelsohn, Eric (Mrs.), 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Metropolitan Youth Commission (Portland), 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Metropolitan Youth Commission (St. Louis), 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Mexico, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Miami, University of (Florida), 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Michigan State University (East Lansing), 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Michigan State University (Oakland), 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Michigan, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Miller…, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Miller, J. Irwin, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Milliken University, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Minnesota, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Mission Neighborhood Centers, Inc., 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Missouri, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Montana State College, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Montana State University, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Moore…, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Morgan…, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Morris…, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - Murphy…, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - NA-NZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - National…, 1961 (Reel C-1429)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Advisory Council on Juvenile Delinquency, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Agrarian Institute, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Association…, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Association of Social Workers, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Council of Juvenile Court Judges, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Cultural Center, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Education Association, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Industrial Conference Board, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Institute of Health, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Juvenile Court Foundation, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Music Camp, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National Science Foundation, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National University of Colombia, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - National University of Cordoba, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - Near East, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - Nebraska, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - Nelson…, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - New…, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - New York…, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - New York State Association of Registered Private Business Schools, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - New York State Education Department, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - New York University, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - Nigeria, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - North..., 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - Northrop, Eugene R., 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - Northwestern University, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - Notre Dame, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1430)
    - OA-OZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - Office of Education, United States, 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - Ohio State University, 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - Oklahoma State University, 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - Oklahoma, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - Oregon, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - Organization of American States, 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development, 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - Overseas Development Program (Ford Foundation), 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - Overseas Development Program (Ford Foundation) – Standard Reports, 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - Overseas Development Program (Ford Foundation) – Status Reports, 1961 (Reel C-1431)
    - PA-PZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Pakistan, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Pakistan Food and Agricultural Commission, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Pan American Union, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Papanek, Gustav F., 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Pasegian, V.L., 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Passin, Herbert, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Peace Corps, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Peace Research Institute, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Pennsylvania, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Peru, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Peterson…, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Philadelphia Housing Association, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Philippine Islands, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Phillips…, 1961 (Reel C-1432)
    - Pittsburgh, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Platt, William J., 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Population, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - President's Committee on Juvenile Delinquency and Youth Crime, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - President's Science Advisory Committee, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Princeton University, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Public Services Enquiry Commission Puerto Rico, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Puerto Rico, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - QA-QZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - RA-RZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Rheinstein, Max, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Rio Grande do Sul, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Roberts…, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Rochester, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, Santiago, Chile, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Economics Conference, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Rotary International, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - Rutgers University, 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - SA-SCG [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1433)
    - SCHA-SZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1434)
    - Saint Xavier College, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - San Francisco, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Sao Paulo, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Saudi Arabia, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Senate…, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Sister…, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Social Security Administration, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Society…, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - South…, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - South Africa, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Southern California, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Southern Illinois University, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Stanford Research Institute, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Stanford University, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - State Department, United States, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Stevens…, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Stevens Institute of Technology, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Stone…, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Syracuse University, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Syria, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - Syrian Arab Republic, 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - TA-TH [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1435)
    - TI-TZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Taylor…, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Technical…, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Texas, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Thailand, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Thomas…, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Thompson…, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Tibet, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Toronto, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Triffin, Robert, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Tufts, University, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Tulane University, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Tunisia, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Turkey, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - Turner…, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - UA-UZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - UNESCO, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - United..., 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - United Arab Republic, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - United Community Funds and Council of America, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - United Nations, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - United States..., 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - United States Information Agency, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - United States Information Service (Accra, Ghana), 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - United States Information Service (Dar Es Salaam, Tanganyika), 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - United States Information Service (Ivory Coast), 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - United States Information Service (London, England), 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - United States Information Service (Sydney, Australia), 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - University of Ghana, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - University College - Ibadan, Nigeria, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - University College of Tanganyika, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - University of the Valley, 1961 (Reel C-1436)
    - VA-VZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - Virginia Commission on Public Education, 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - Von..., 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - WA-WZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - Wandsworth Prison, 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - Ward, F. Champion, 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - Washington (Organizations)..., 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - George Washington University, 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - Washington University, St. Louis, 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - Washington University, Seattle, 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - Wayne State University, 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - West..., 1961 (Reel C-1437)
    - West Virginia, 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - Western..., 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - Western Reserve University, 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - Wichita, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - Wisconsin, University of, 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - Woods..., 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - World Affairs Council of Northern California, 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - Wyzanski, Charles E. Jr., 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - Xavier University, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - YA-YZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - Yale University, 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - Yarmolinsky, Adam, 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - Young..., 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - ZA-ZZ [General File], 1961 (Reel C-1438)
    - Bibliography of Related Materials, General Correspondence, 1961 (Reel C-1438)
      List of books, pamphlets, articles, reports, etc. related to the General Correspondence files for 1961.
- General Correspondence, 1962
  - A- American Council on Education, 1962 (Reel C-1439)
  - American Federation of the Arts - COM, 1962 (Reel C-1440)
  - CON - DZ, 1962 (Reel C-1441)
  - Dallas - Greenough, 1962 (Reel C-1442)
  - H - Kingsley, 1962 (Reel C-1443)
  - L - National University., 1962 (Reel C-1444)
  - National University of Colombia (Bogota) - PE, 1962 (Reel C-1445)
  - PF - Rutgers Univ., 1962 (Reel C-1446)
  - S - SZ, 1962 (Reel C-1447)
  - T - United States Commission for UNESCO, 1962 (Reel C-1448)
  - University - Z, 1962 (Reel C-1449)
- General Correspondence, 1963
  - A - Business Council for International, 1963 (Reel C-1450)
  - C - Columbia Univ., 1963 (Reel C-1451)
  - Commerce Dept. of - Federation of Protestant, 1963 (Reel C-1452)
  - Franklin Publications Inc. - Huntly, J., 1963 (Reel C-1453)
  - I - Jones, 1963 (Reel C-1454)
  - K - MT, 1963 (Reel C-1455)
  - MU - National Recreation Assoc., 1963 (Reel C-1456)
  - National Science Foundation - PE, 1963 (Reel C-1457)
  - PF - RH, 1963 (Reel C-1458)
  - RI - Stanford Research Inst., 1963 (Reel C-1459)
  - Stanford Univ. - Utah, Univ. of, 1963 (Reel C-1460)
  - V - Z, 1963 (Reel C-1461)
- General Correspondence, 1964
  - A - AL, 1964 (Reel C-1462)
  - AM - Assoc. for Educational Data Systems, 1964 (Reel C-1463)
  - Assoc. of Graduate Schools - CN, 1964 (Reel C-1464)
  - CO - Commission, 1964 (Reel C-1465)
  - Committee - Educational Training Service, 1964 (Reel C-1466)
  - Efferson, J - HD, 1964 (Reel C-1467)
  - HE - Inter-American Inst., 1964 (Reel C-1468)
  - International A - Lindsay, K, 1964 (Reel C-1469)
  - Lloyd College - ND, 1964 (Reel C-1470)
  - NE - North Carolina, 1964 (Reel C-1471)
  - North Toledo Community - Peru, 1964 (Reel C-1472)
  - Philadelphia - SO, 1964 (Reel C-1473)
  - SP - Syracuse Univ., 1964 (Reel C-1474)
  - Systems Development Corp - WZ, 1964 (Reel C-1475)
  - Waschman - Z, 1964 (Reel C-1476)
- General Correspondence, 1965
  - Economic Development and Administration Program (EDA), 1965; 1
    - A-B, 1965 (Reel C-1485)
    - C-W, 1965 (Reel C-1486)
    - X - Z, 1965 (Reel C-1487)
  - Education Program, 1965; 2
    - A - Columbus Public School, 1965 (Reel C-1487)
    - Comm. Program - Learn. Inst. Of North Carolina, 1965 (Reel C-1488)
    - Lincoln University - POG, 1965 (Reel C-1489)
    - Port - Youth Opp. Unlimited, 1965 (Reel C-1490)